Guide to the Miscellaneous Manuscripts Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- M, Series VI
  - Middleton, James Collection, 1871-1927 (Box 40, Folder 869)
  - Miles, Nelson Appleton, undated (Box 40, Folder 870)
  - Miller, John, 1833 (Box 40, Folder 871)
  - Miller, John Krepps, 1848 (Box 40, Folder 872)
  - Miller, Warner, 1884 (Box 40, Folder 873)
  - Mills, Eliza B. (Smith), 1824-1852 (Box 40, Folder 874)
  - Mills, Isaac, 1818 (Box 40, Folder 875)
  - Minor, Edward E. Collection, 1743-1773 (Box 40, Folder 876)
  - Minor, William Thomas, 1874 (Box 40, Folder 877)
  - Mitchell, Samuel Latham, 1822 (Box 40, Folder 878)
  - Mitchell, Simeon, 1782 (Box 40, Folder 879)
  - Mitchell, Stephen, 1831 (Box 40, Folder 880)
  - Mittwoch, Eugen, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 881)
  - Moffat, Reuben Curtis, 1882 (Box 40, Folder 882)
  - Mok, P. K., 1944 (Box 41, Folder 883)
  - Molly (Sloop), 1752 (Box 41, Folder 884)
  - Moltke, Helmut Karl Bernhard, Graf von, 1871 (Box 41, Folder 885)
  - Mommsen, Theodor, undated (Box 41, Folder 886)
  - Monroe, James (1758-1831), 1819 (Box 41, Folder 887)
  - Monroe, James (1799-1870), 1853 (Box 41, Folder 888)
  - Monvel, R. B. (Tremolieres) de, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 889)
  - Moody, Dwight Lyman, 1889 (Box 41, Folder 890)
  - Moore, Robert, 1818 (Box 41, Folder 891)
  - Moorish Science Temple of America, [1954?] (Box 41, Folder 892)
  - Morgan, Daniel, 1798 (Box 41, Folder 893)
  - Morgan, Edwin Barber, 1866 (Box 41, Folder 894)
  - Morgan, John Hill, 1937-1942, undated (Box 41, Folder 895)
  - Mornand, Felix, 1838-1863, undated (Box 41, Folder 896)
  - Morris, Angela J., 1911-1942, undated (Box 41, Folder 897)
  - Morris, James, 1814, undated (Box 41, Folder 898)
  - Morris, Richard, 1786 (Box 41, Folder 899)
  - Morris, Robert (1734-1806), 1795, 1797 (Box 41, Folder 900)
  - Morris, Robert (1745-1815), 1808 (Box 41, Folder 901)
  - Morrison, John Henry, 1850-1860 (Box 41, Folder 902)
  - Morrow, Arthur, 1829 (Box 41, Folder 903)
  - Morse, Alexander Porter, 1882 (Box 41, Folder 904)
  - Morse, Gardner, 1850, undated (Box 41, Folder 905)
  - Morse, George B. and Louisa L., 1851 (Box 41, Folder 906)
  - Mortimer, Cordelia, 1835 (Box 41, Folder 907)
  - Morton, Samuel George, 1851 (Box 41, Folder 908)
  - Moser, Ernst, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 909)
  - Mott, John Raleigh, 1913-1917, 1930, undated (Box 41, Folder 910)
  - Mott, Lucretia (Coffin), [1852?] (Box 41, Folder 911)
  - Mott, Samuel, 1762-1811 (Box 41, Folder 912)
  - Munchhausen, A. von, 1853 (Box 41, Folder 913)
  - Murphy, Blanche Elizabeth Mary Annunciata (Noel), undated (Box 41, Folder 914)
  - Murray, Mary S., 1860 (Box 41, Folder 915)
  - Muthesius, Karl, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 916)
- N - O, Series VII
  - Nagler, Alois Maria, undated (Box 42, Folder 917)
  - Nashville, Indiana Methodist Episcopal Church, 1873 (Box 42, Folder 918)
  - Nation, Carry Amelia (Moore) Gloyd, undated (Box 42, Folder 919)
  - National Southwest Associated University, Kunming, China, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 920)
  - Nausester, Walter, 1907, undated (Box 42, Folder 921)
  - Neffsville, Pennsylvania, 1814 (Box 42, Folder 922)
  - Nettleton, William L. and Henry, 1834 (Box 42, Folder 923)
  - Neuville, Alphonse Marie de, undated (Box 42, Folder 924)
  - New Constitution (fishing vessel), 1789 (Box 42, Folder 925)
  - New Hampshire, 1838-1880, undated (Box 42, Folder 926)
  - New Haven. Kent Hall, 1899-1901 (Box 42, Folder 927)
  - New Jersey, 1792-1868 (Box 42, Folder 928-929)
  - New Orleans Club, 1864 (Box 42, Folder 930)
  - New York City. Mayor's Court, 1800 (Box 42, Folder 931)
  - New York State, 1675-1932 (Box 42, Folder 932-934)
  - New York and Erie Railroad, undated (Box 42, Folder 935)
  - New York Historical Society, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 936)
  - New York Infantry, undated (Box 42, Folder 937)
  - New York Misc. Mss., 1792-1847, undated (Box 42, Folder 938)
  - Newall, William G., 1846-1856 (Box 42, Folder 939)
  - Newcomb, Simon, 1896 (Box 42, Folder 940)
  - Newton, Elbert F., 1928-1935, undated (Box 42, Folder 941)
  - Newton, Sarah, 1838-1850 (Box 42, Folder 942)
  - Nicholl, J., 1809 (Box 42, Folder 943)
  - Nichols Family, 1733-1808 (Box 42, Folder 944)
  - Nicholson, Jonathan, estate of, 1865-1866 (Box 42, Folder 945)
  - Nicolay, John George, 1900, undated (Box 42, Folder 946)
  - Nicoll, Mrs. Benjamin, [1911?] (Box 42, Folder 947)
  - Nightingale, Florence, 1872, undated (Box 42, Folder 948)
  - Nilen, Nils Fredrik, 1890, undated (Box 42, Folder 949)
  - Noble, Oliver, 1776 (Box 42, Folder 950)
  - Northrop, Bennett Fairchild, 1827 (Box 42, Folder 951)
  - Northrop Family Collection, 1821-1878 (Box 43, Folder 952)
  - Norton, Charles Eliot, 1900 (Box 43, Folder 953)
  - Norton, Joshua Abraham, 1874 (Box 43, Folder 954)
  - Nott, Charles D., 1884 (Box 43, Folder 955)
  - Nova Scotia. Baptist-Home Missionary Union, 1873 (Box 43, Folder 956)
  - Noyes, Burr, 1824-1825 (Box 43, Folder 957)
  - Noyes, Julia C., 1857-1877 (Box 43, Folder 958)
  - O'Brien, Arthur Henry, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 959)
  - O'Callaghan, Edmund Bailey, 1860-1871 (Box 43, Folder 960)
  - O'Conor, Charles, 1883 (Box 43, Folder 961)
  - Örsted, Hans Christian, 1847 (Box 43, Folder 962)
  - Ogden, Aaron, 1803 (Box 43, Folder 963)
  - Ogden, Alfred, 1931-1932 (Box 43, Folder 964)
  - Olds, John, 1769 (Box 43, Folder 965)
  - Ollivier, Emile, undated (Box 43, Folder 966)
  - Olney, Ethan, 1818 (Box 43, Folder 967)
  - O'Reilly, Mary Boyle, 1900 (Box 43, Folder 968)
  - Otis, Elmer, 1858 (Box 43, Folder 969)
  - Otis, Richard D., 1962 (Box 43, Folder 970)
  - Ottendorfer, Anna (Behr), 1881 (Box 43, Folder 971)
- P - R, Series VIII
  - Page, Samuel Davis, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 972)
  - Painter, Thomas, 1836-1842 (Box 44, Folder 973)
  - Palfrey, John Gorham, 1846, 1855 (Box 44, Folder 974)
  - Palmer, [Kate?], [1862?] (Box 44, Folder 975)
  - Palmer, Lillian McNeill, undated (Box 44, Folder 976)
  - Paradise, Nathaniel Burton, 1782, undated (Box 44, Folder 977)
  - Paravey, Charles Hippolyte De, 1820-1833, undated (Box 44, Folder 978)
  - Park, John Duane, 1858 (Box 44, Folder 979)
  - Park, Lawrence, 1918 (Box 44, Folder 980)
  - Parker, George C., 1930 (Box 44, Folder 981)
  - Parker, John Henry, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 982)
  - Parkhurst, Helen, 1915-1928, undated (Box 44, Folder 983)
  - Parrott, Enoch Greenleafe, 1832, 1844 (Box 44, Folder 984)
  - Parsons, George W., 1878 (Box 44, Folder 985)
  - Patterson Family Collection, 1699-1839 (Box 44, Folder 986)
  - Pawarendrramesr, S. P., 1861 (Box 44, Folder 987)
  - Pearsall, Thomas, 1775 (Box 44, Folder 988)
  - Peck, Henry Brandagee, 1859-1865, undated (Box 44, Folder 989)
  - Peck, P. F. M., 1839 (Box 44, Folder 990)
  - Peck and Phelps, 1826-1858 (Box 44, Folder 991)
  - Pelouse, Léon Germain, 1888 (Box 44, Folder 992)
  - Pène du Bois, Henri, 1892, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 993)
  - Pennington, Harper, 1909-1910, undated (Box 44, Folder 994)
  - Perkins, George Leonard, 1861 (Box 44, Folder 995)
  - Perkins, Levi, 1816 (Box 44, Folder 996)
  - Perkins, Nathan, 1778-1824, undated (Box 44, Folder 997)
  - Perrin, Lavalette, 1843-1847, 1867-1872 (Box 45, Folder 998)
  - Perry, Matthew Calbraith, 1849-1850, 1857 (Box 45, Folder 999)
  - Pestalozzi, Johann Heinrich, undated (Box 45, Folder 1000)
  - Peters, Richard, 1800 (Box 45, Folder 1001)
  - Petit, Pierre, 1830 (Box 45, Folder 1002)
  - Petrie, William Matthew Flinders, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 1003)
  - Pforzheimer, Walter Lionel, 1954-1963 (Box 45, Folder 1004)
  - Phelps, Edward John, 1885-[1893?] (Box 45, Folder 1005)
  - Phelps, Lancelot, 1837 (Box 45, Folder 1006)
  - [Phelps, Lawrence?], 1878-1879 (Box 45, Folder 1007)
  - Phelps, Olivia (Mrs. Anson G.), 1856-1863 (Box 45, Folder 1008)
  - Phillips, Henry Albert, 1926 (Box 45, Folder 1009)
  - Phillips, Wendell, 1881 (Box 45, Folder 1010)
  - Phillips, William, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 1011)
  - Pichon, Emilie (Brongniart), 1815 (Box 45, Folder 1012)
  - Pickett, Louise A., 1901 (Box 45, Folder 1013)
  - Pierce, Franklin, 1853, undated (Box 45, Folder 1014)
  - Pierpont, John, 1648 (Box 45, Folder 1015)
  - Pierrepont, John Jay, 1871 (Box 45, Folder 1016)
  - Pierson, Abraham, 1776 (Box 45, Folder 1017)
  - Pillsbury, John Sargeant, 1879, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 1018)
  - Pilsbury, Charles A., 1858 (Box 45, Folder 1019)
  - Pilsbury, Moses C., 1826 (Box 45, Folder 1020)
  - Pilsbury, Timothy, 1848 (Box 45, Folder 1021)
  - Pinckney, Charles, 1792 (Box 45, Folder 1022)
  - Pinckney, David J., undated (Box 45, Folder 1023)
  - Pinelli, Luca, undated (Box 45, Folder 1024)
  - Piper, William Adam, 1876 (Box 45, Folder 1025)
  - Pitkin, William, 1767 (Box 45, Folder 1026)
  - Pitt, William, 1788 (Box 45, Folder 1027)
  - Platt, Orville Hitchcock, 1884-1902 (Box 45, Folder 1028)
  - Pleasants, Samuel, 1784-1799 (Box 45, Folder 1029)
  - Polymnia Literary Society, Brooklyn, N.Y., Circa 1869 (Box 46, Folder 1030)
  - Pool, Mrs. E., 1808 (Box 46, Folder 1031)
  - Poore, Benjamin Perley, 1872-1883 (Box 46, Folder 1032)
  - Porter, Cole Albert, Circa 1914 (Box 46, Folder 1033)
  - Porter, David, 1827 (Box 46, Folder 1034)
  - Porter, John Addison (1822-1866), 1855-1860, undated (Box 46, Folder 1035)
  - Porter, John Addison (1856-1900), 1897 (Box 46, Folder 1036)
  - Porter, Josias Leslie, 1872 (Box 46, Folder 1037)
  - Porter, Martha Day, 1892-1919 (Box 46, Folder 1038)
  - Porter, Samuel, 1885 (Box 46, Folder 1039)
  - Porter, Sarah, 1856 (Box 46, Folder 1040)
  - Potter, Jessie B., 1921 (Box 46, Folder 1041)
  - Pottle, Frederick Albert, 1934 (Box 46, Folder 1042)
  - Potts, George, 1851 (Box 46, Folder 1043)
  - Powers, Cyrus, 1858 (Box 46, Folder 1044)
  - Pratt, Agnes Rothery, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 1045)
  - Praxis Judiciaria, undated (Box 46, Folder 1046)
  - Prescott, Benjamin F., 1888 (Box 46, Folder 1047)
  - Preston, Nathan, undated (Box 46, Folder 1048)
  - Price, Waterhouse & Company, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 1049)
  - Prince, LeBaron Bradford, 1892-1893, 1920 (Box 46, Folder 1050)
  - Pringle, James R., 1871-1875 (Box 46, Folder 1051)
  - Proctor, Henry, 1772 (Box 46, Folder 1052)
  - Prussia. Herzogthum Magdeburg. Landrats-Amt, 1785 (Box 46, Folder 1053)
  - Pumphrey, Ralph Everett, 1931 (Box 46, Folder 1054)
  - Putnam, G. P., Sons, 1852, 1894-1895 (Box 46, Folder 1055)
  - Putnam, John Graves, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1056)
  - Putnam, Samuel, 1790, 1797 (Box 46, Folder 1057)
  - Pyle, Ernest Taylor, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 1058)
  - Pynchon, Thomas Ruggles, 1850, undated (Box 46, Folder 1059)
  - Pynchon Family, 1728-1886, undated (Box 46, Folder 1060)
  - Quatrefages de Bréau, Armand de, 1889-1891 (Box 46, Folder 1061)
  - Quincy, Elisa S., 1834 (Box 46, Folder 1062)
  - Raffells, Ed V. H., 1936-1952 (Box 47, Folder 1063)
  - Ralston, Andrew, 1867 (Box 47, Folder 1064)
  - Rand, Richard, 1829 (Box 47, Folder 1065)
  - Randolph, Edmund, 1805 (Box 47, Folder 1066)
  - Randolph, John, 1807 (Box 47, Folder 1067)
  - Randolph, Paschal Beverly, 1869-1870 (Box 47, Folder 1068)
  - Rawson, Edward Kirk, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 1069)
  - Raymond, Edward Artemus, 1841-1845 (Box 47, Folder 1070)
  - Raymond, S., undated (Box 47, Folder 1071)
  - Record, Samuel James Collection, 1831-1842 (Box 47, Folder 1072)
  - Reekie, Charles, 1899 (Box 47, Folder 1073)
  - Rees, Thomas Ifor, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 1074)
  - Reich, William Charles, 1889 (Box 47, Folder 1075)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1870 (Box 47, Folder 1076)
  - Renner, Robert, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 1077)
  - Reynolds, William, 1846 (Box 47, Folder 1078)
  - Rhead, Louis, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 1079)
  - Ridge, Walter B. K., 1939-1948 (Box 47, Folder 1080)
  - Ritter, John, 1863 (Box 47, Folder 1081)
  - Robbins, Asher, 1824-1840 (Box 47, Folder 1082)
  - Robert de Vaugondy, Didier, 1779 (Box 47, Folder 1083)
  - Robertson, Archibald, 1892 (Box 47, Folder 1084)
  - Robinson, Charles N., 1910, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 1085)
  - Robinson, Edgar Stewart, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 1086)
  - Robinson, Edmund Randolph, 1885 (Box 47, Folder 1087)
  - Robinson, Harmon, 1811-1852 (Box 47, Folder 1088)
  - Robinson, Henry, 1832, 1838 (Box 47, Folder 1089)
  - Rochambeau, Jean Baptiste, 1771 (Box 47, Folder 1090)
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1891, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 1091)
  - Rodney, Caesar Augustus, undated (Box 47, Folder 1092)
  - Roe, Benjamin, 1790 (Box 47, Folder 1093)
  - Rogers, William, 1844 (Box 47, Folder 1094)
  - Rohde, Erwin, 1838 (Box 47, Folder 1095)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1942, undated (Box 47, Folder 1096)
  - Roosevelt, James John Jr., 1811-1814 (Box 47, Folder 1097)
  - Roosevelt, Robert Barnwell, 1871 (Box 47, Folder 1098)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1883-1913 (Box 47, Folder 1099-1100)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1914-1918, undated (Box 47, Folder 1101)
  - Rose, John Carter, 1924 (Box 48, Folder 1102)
  - Rousseau, Arthur, 1902 (Box 48, Folder 1103)
  - Rowell, John F., 1848-1850 (Box 48, Folder 1104)
  - Rowell, Moses Jr., undated (Box 48, Folder 1105)
  - Rowell, Teresina Pecke, undated (Box 48, Folder 1106)
  - Rowland, Thomas Fitch, 1903 (Box 48, Folder 1107)
  - Rubakin, Nikolai Aleksandrovich, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 1108)
  - Ruggles, Timothy, 1766 (Box 48, Folder 1109)
  - Rush, Richard, 1846 (Box 48, Folder 1110)
  - Russell, James, 1702 (Box 48, Folder 1111)
  - Russell, Noadiah, 1687 (Box 48, Folder 1112)
  - Russell, William Augustus, undated (Box 48, Folder 1113)
  - Russell, William Huntington, 1869 (Box 48, Folder 1114)
  - HMS Russell, 1904-1906 (Box 48, Folder 1115)
  - Russian Miscellanea, undated (Box 48, Folder 1116)
  - Ryder, B. H., 1914-1917 (Box 48, Folder 1117)
  - Ryno, Park, 1786 (Box 48, Folder 1118)
- S, Series IX
  - Sabine, Jane Downes (Kelly), 1940 (Box 49, Folder 1119)
  - Sackett, William Henry, 1799-1803 (Box 49, Folder 1120)
  - Sage, Ebenezer, 1809 (Box 49, Folder 1121)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Homer Schiff, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 1122)
  - Saltonstall, Gurdon family, 1716, 1761-1792, undated (Box 49, Folder 1123)
  - Sanborn, Marjorie, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 1124)
  - Sànchez, Florencio, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1125)
  - Sands, Henry Berton, 1885 (Box 49, Folder 1126)
  - Sangamon and Morgan Railroad Company, 1848-1849 (Box 49, Folder 1127)
  - Savannah (ship), 1868 (Box 49, Folder 1128)
  - Sayce, Archibald Henry, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 1129)
  - Schäffle, Albert Eberhard Friedrich, undated (Box 49, Folder 1130)
  - Schapsmeier, Frederick Herman, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 1131)
  - Schiller, Herman, 1877 (Box 49, Folder 1132)
  - Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich, 1859 (Box 49, Folder 1133)
  - Schoolcraft, Henry Rowe, 1849-1860 (Box 49, Folder 1134)
  - Schoonmaker, Cornelia Marius (Groen), 1830 (Box 49, Folder 1135)
  - Schott, Sigmund, undated (Box 49, Folder 1136)
  - Schreyvogel, Charles, 1903 (Box 49, Folder 1137)
  - Schroeder, John Frederick, 1838 (Box 49, Folder 1138)
  - Scot, Robert, 1792 (Box 49, Folder 1139)
  - Scott, Charles Ernest, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1140)
  - Scott, William Bell, 1886 (Box 49, Folder 1441)
  - Scott, Winfield, 1839, 1861 (Box 49, Folder 1142)
  - Scovell, Noah, 1787-1819, undated (Box 49, Folder 1143)
  - Scranton, Erastus, 1834 (Box 49, Folder 1144)
  - Sears, Ebenezer, 1750, 1769 (Box 49, Folder 1145)
  - Sears, Lorenzo, 1898 (Box 49, Folder 1146)
  - Sedgwick, Theodore, 1853 (Box 49, Folder 1147)
  - Seebach, Marie, 1871 (Box 49, Folder 1148)
  - Seeley, Aaron Family, 1818-1859, undated (Box 49, Folder 1149)
  - Seep, Albert E., undated (Box 50, Folder 1150)
  - Select Collumbian Society, Penn., 1823 (Box 50, Folder 1151)
  - Serebriakov-Elboursky, Paul V., 1928 (Box 50, Folder 1152)
  - Sermon, 1734 (Box 50, Folder 1153)
  - Seward, Frederick William, 1888 (Box 50, Folder 1154)
  - Seward, William Henry, 1850-1865, undated (Box 50, Folder 1155)
  - Seymour, Mary K. Family, 1855-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1156)
  - Seymour, Thomas Hart, 1851, 1854 (Box 50, Folder 1157)
  - Shaker Hymnal, undated (Box 50, Folder 1158)
  - Shattuck, John David, 1914, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 1159)
  - Shaw-Stewart, Patrick, 1918-1937, undated (Box 50, Folder 1160)
  - Shay's Rebellion, 1787-1788 (Box 50, Folder 1161)
  - Sheffield, Joseph Earl, 1875-1876 (Box 50, Folder 1162)
  - Sheldor, Franklin J., 1913, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 1163)
  - Shepard, George C., 1851 (Box 50, Folder 1164)
  - Sheridan, Philip Henry, 1865, 1876-1885 (Box 50, Folder 1165-1166)
  - Sherman, William Tecumseh, [1865?]-1874| (Box 50, Folder 1167)
  - Shipman, [C.?], 1862 (Box 50, Folder 1168)
  - Shipman, William Davis, 1853-1862 (Box 50, Folder 1169)
  - Short, J., 1854 (Box 50, Folder 1170)
  - Sickles, Daniel Edgar, 1866 (Box 51, Folder 1171)
  - Sigourney, Charles, 1815 (Box 51, Folder 1172)
  - Sikes, Walter W., 1934 (Box 51, Folder 1173)
  - Silliman, Jonathan, 1814 (Box 51, Folder 1174)
  - Silliman, Thomas, 1818 (Box 51, Folder 1175)
  - Silver, William, 1833-1859, undated (Box 51, Folder 1176)
  - Simonds, William Edgar, 1889 (Box 51, Folder 1177)
  - Sinclair, A. McLean, 1828, undated (Box 51, Folder 1178)
  - Skinner, Aaron Nichols, 1842-1854 (Box 51, Folder 1179)
  - Slater, John F., 1840, 1878 (Box 51, Folder 1180)
  - Slosson, William, 1828 (Box 51, Folder 1181)
  - Smales, Herbert, 1850 (Box 51, Folder 1182)
  - Smith, Almon, 1834 (Box 51, Folder 1183)
  - Smith, Benjamin Eli, 1882-1913, 1954, undated (Box 51, Folder 1184)
  - Smith, Caleb Jr., 1802-1818 (Box 51, Folder 1185)
  - Smith, Channing M., 1922 (Box 51, Folder 1186)
  - Smith, George Williamson, 1887 (Box 51, Folder 1187)
  - Smith, Goldwin, 1867 (Box 51, Folder 1188)
  - Smith, James, 1797 (Box 51, Folder 1189)
  - Smith, James Perry Family, 1720-1887, undated (Box 51, Folder 1190)
  - Smith, Nathan, 1823, undated (Box 51, Folder 1191)
  - Smith, Nathaniel, 1796-1807 (Box 51, Folder 1192)
  - Smith, Perry, 1839-1842, undated (Box 51, Folder 1193)
  - Smith, Richard Somers, 1839-1842, undated (Box 51, Folder 1194)
  - Smith, Samuel Harrison, 1812 (Box 51, Folder 1195)
  - Smith, Truman, 1839, 1848 (Box 51, Folder 1196)
  - Smyth, Dame Ethel Mary, 1914-1939 (Box 51, Folder 1197)
  - Smythe, Roland M., 1876, 1892-1899, undated (Box 51, Folder 1198)
  - Snyder, Walter Francis, undated (Box 52, Folder 1199)
  - Society for the Reformation of Juvenile Delinquents of the City of New York, 1835 (Box 52, Folder 1200)
  - South Carolina. Probate Court, 1887 (Box 52, Folder 1201)
  - Spain, 1540-1543 (Box 52, Folder 1202)
  - Sparks, Jared, 1835 (Box 52, Folder 1203)
  - Spear, Thomas G., 1833-1854, undated (Box 52, Folder 1204)
  - Sperry, Charles Stillman, undated (Box 52, Folder 1205)
  - Sperry, Isaac L., 1860-1869, undated (Box 52, Folder 1206)
  - Spooner, Ephraim, 1775 (Box 52, Folder 1207)
  - Spooner, Samuel Brigham, 1849-1853 (Box 52, Folder 1208-1209)
  - Sprague, William Buell, 1830 (Box 52, Folder 1210)
  - Sproule, W., 1884 (Box 52, Folder 1211)
  - Squier, Ephraim George, 1846 (Box 52, Folder 1212)
  - Stanbury and Galway, N.Y., 1855 (Box 52, Folder 1213)
  - Stanhope, John, 1754 (Box 52, Folder 1241)
  - Stanley, Sir Henry Morton, 1874, 1878 (Box 52, Folder 1215)
  - Stark, Gilbert Little, undated (Box 52, Folder 1216)
  - Starkweather, Henry Howard, 1875 (Box 52, Folder 1217)
  - Starr Family, 1742-1842, undated (Box 52, Folder 1218)
  - Stauffer, Jacob, 1826 (Box 52, Folder 1219)
  - Stearns, Winfred Alden, undated (Box 53, Folder 1220)
  - Stebbins, Laura (Allen), 1798-1805, undated (Box 53, Folder 1221)
  - Steinbart, Gustav, 1857-1858 (Box 53, Folder 1222)
  - Steller, Georg Wilhelm, 1741 (Box 53, Folder 1223)
  - Stephens, Alexander Hamilton, 1845 (Box 53, Folder 1224)
  - Stetson, Gushing, 1909 (Box 53, Folder 1225)
  - Steuben, Friedrich Wilhelm Ludolf Gerhard Augustin, Baron von, 1786 (Box 53, Folder 1226)
  - Stevens, Hiram, 1839-1860 (Box 53, Folder 1227)
  - Stevens, Orville H., 1842-1851, undated (Box 53, Folder 1228)
  - Stevens, Thomas A., 1954-1964 (Box 53, Folder 1229)
  - Stewart, Charles, 1857 (Box 53, Folder 1230)
  - Stewart, Daniel K., 1833 (Box 53, Folder 1231)
  - Stewart family, undated (Box 53, Folder 1232)
  - Steyne, Alan Nathaniel, undated (Box 54, Folder 1233)
  - Stiles, Ezra, 1817-1844 (Box 54, Folder 1234)
  - Stiles, Ezra Griswold, undated (Box 54, Folder 1235)
  - Stillé, Alfred, 1844 (Box 54, Folder 1236)
  - Stimson, Henry Albert, 1878-1966, undated (Box 55, Folder 1237)
  - Stockton, Richard, 1770 (Box 55, Folder 1238)
  - Stoddard family, 1709-1864, undated (Box 55, Folder 1239)
  - Stoeckel, Carl, 1888 (Box 55, Folder 1240)
  - Storrs family, 1781-1853 (Box 55, Folder 1241)
  - Strathcona and Mount Royal, Donald Alexander Smith, 1st Baron, 1896, 1908 (Box 55, Folder 1242)
  - Strong, George Washington, 1802-1803 (Box 55, Folder 1243)
  - Strong, Nathan, 1773-1814 (Box 55, Folder 1244)
  - Strong, W., undated (Box 55, Folder 1245)
  - Struensee, Johann Friedrich, Count, 1869 (Box 55, Folder 1246)
  - Sturges, S., 1866 (Box 55, Folder 1247)
  - Stuyvesant, Nicholas William, 1765 (Box 55, Folder 1248)
  - Styles, Daniel, 1836-1877, undated (Box 55, Folder 1249)
  - Styria, Carinthia and Krain, 1594 (Box 55, Folder 1250)
  - Sumner, Charles, 1852-1856, undated (Box 55, Folder 1251)
  - Swanville, Maine, Tax collector, 1868, undated (Box 55, Folder 1252)
  - Swift family, 1801-1832, 1852 (Box 55, Folder 1253)
  - Symonds, John, 1767-1768 (Box 55, Folder 1254)
- T, Series X
  - Taft, Robert Alphonso, 1939, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 255)
  - Taintor, John A., 1850 (Box 56, Folder 1256)
  - Talbot, P., 1802 (Box 56, Folder 1257)
  - Talcott, Sebastian Visscher, 1853 (Box 56, Folder 1258)
  - Talleyrand-Périgord, Charles Maurice de, Prince de Bénévent, 1821 (Box 56, Folder 1259)
  - Tallmadge, Benjamin, 1776-1810 (Box 56, Folder 1260)
  - Tallmadge, Frederick Augustus, 1866 (Box 56, Folder 1261)
  - Tanney, Augustus, 1823 (Box 56, Folder 1262)
  - Tappan, Samuel F., 1881-1882 (Box 56, Folder 1263)
  - Tarchiani, Alberto, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 1264)
  - Taylor, Bayard, 1876 (Box 56, Folder 1265)
  - Taylor, John Metcalf, 1900 (Box 56, Folder 1266)
  - Taylor, Rowse, 1811 (Box 56, Folder 1267)
  - Terry Family, 1811-1849, undated (Box 56, Folder 1268)
  - Terhune, Mary Virginia (Hawes), 1873 (Box 56, Folder 1269)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1846-1877 (Box 56, Folder 1270)
  - Thacker, J. and Co., Australia, 1853 (Box 56, Folder 1271)
  - Thomas, David, 1803-1854 (Box 56, Folder 1272)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 1273)
  - Thompson, Henry J. H., 1862-1865, undated (Box 56, Folder 1274)
  - Thompson, Dr. Isaac, 1817 (Box 56, Folder 1275)
  - Thorburn, Septimus Smet, undated (Box 56, Folder 1276)
  - Thorp, Eliakim, 1824-1837 (Box 56, Folder 1277)
  - Throop, George Hawley, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 1278)
  - Thurston, Carl Hammond Philander, 1928-1946, undated (Box 56, Folder 1279)
  - Tillotson, Edward Sweetser, 1900 (Box 56, Folder 1280)
  - Tilton, James, 1855-1856, 1893 (Box 57, Folder 1281)
  - Tomlin, Olive Bird, 1917, 1940-1950 (Box 57, Folder 1282)
  - Torlonia and Co., Rome, 1824 (Box 57, Folder 1283)
  - Torrance, Arthur, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 1284)
  - Toussaint Louverture, Francois Dominique, 1800-1801, undated (Box 57, Folder 1285)
  - Townsend, Benjamin R., 1866, 1895-1898 (Box 57, Folder 1286)
  - Tracy, Susanna, 1816 (Box 57, Folder 1287)
  - Trask, Jane Cruickshank (O'Farrell), undated (Box 57, Folder 1288)
  - Traveller (steamer), 1853 (Box 57, Folder 1289)
  - Treat, Salmon, 1694, 1716 (Box 57, Folder 1290)
  - Troup, Robert, 1805 (Box 57, Folder 1291)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1959 (Box 57, Folder 1292)
  - Trumbull, Henry Clay, 1885 (Box 57, Folder 1293)
  - Trumbull, Samuel, 1808 (Box 57, Folder 1294)
  - Tuck, J. W., 1857 (Box 57, Folder 1295)
  - Turnbull, Robert, 1862 (Box 57, Folder 1296)
  - Turner, Lewis McKenzie, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 1297)
  - Tuttle, Lucius J. H., 1830 (Box 57, Folder 1298)
  - Tyler, John, 1842 (Box 57, Folder 1299)